this is how to Echo out sound in premiere pro
[Music] so first you need to make a cut on the
audio you want the Reverb effect on and you can
delete the left overs now right click on the audio
and then go to nest and then click on okay to
add Echo go to effects and then search Reverb
and then apply the studio Reverb effect to the
nested clip with the layer selected go to effect
controls and then click on edit inside this
window you can choose from different presets
if you want or you can simply increase the
Decay to get Echo you will now notice that
we still don't have any Reverb or Echo and that
we can't extend the audio clip to fix this double
click on the nested layer to open it and then go
to the start of it now go to the project panel
and then click on new item and then select
transparent video and click on okay you can
now drag the transparent video to the timeline
and then extend it a bit and then you can exit
out of the layer this will allow us to expand
an the layer and give us this Reverb effect